Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you want it,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day,
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece, I'll be
the first. I'll put it.
Be so bad, I could first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it waiting.
In a world I'm feeling alive.
But I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We go.
I was quite taken aback by the news.
But perhaps that is my ignorance speaking.
Do you believe it's a wise decision?
Big Mom is ruthless, but
she lets us do as we please.
It's fine for now.
Hmm, I see.
Then if I may be frank once more,
it surprises me that
you're comfortable taking
orders from anyone other
than fish or tiger.
No, it's alright.
I'm not above working under someone
else's authority by any means.
That's the way it works in the new world.
If a captain wishes to guarantee
the safety of his crew,
allying with the four emperors
is the best way to do it.
Is that all?
It seems to me that you're doing it
for the good of Fishman Island as well.
Even after Whitebeard's passing,
our kingdom remains safe
under Big Mom's protection,
because you connected us with her.
We can't thank you
enough for that, Jinbei.
Oh no, please don't thank me.
We have a responsibility to make
sure Fishman Island is protected,
even if we are wanted criminals.
Having said that,
I believe that the time may have come for
me to terminate my
partnership with Big Maw.
Ah, so you're going to
accept Luffy's invitation?
Hey, Team Bae, what do you say, pal?
Will you join my crew?
Yes, I have made my decision.
But the pirate world operates through...
honor, not contracts.
We'd much rather make a verbal agreement
over drinks than sign documents.
Because of that,
we mustn't go breaking such agreements
without careful consideration.
What concerns me the most
is the possibility that
Big Mom will direct your
anger at Fishman Arthur.
Honestly, Gene Bay, you need not feel
responsible for every little thing.
If such an incident comes
to pass then so be it
I have a plan why just
today we took in 70 000
fierce newcomers from
Fishman District they'll
make fine soldiers do
not worry about his job
and in the event we lose the protection
of Big Mom's Jolly Roger there
is another flag I'd like to use
instead one with a Straw Hat might
look nice don't you think Jungle
couldn't agree more I'm partial to that
flag myself your
majesty forgive me
but we have a serious problem Hmm?
It's terrible!
What's the matter, Minister of the Right?
I remember something from long ago.
With all due respect, sir,
we made a mistake by letting the Straw
Hat Pirates keep that stolen treasure.
Hmm?
I'm not certain if they
found it yet, but if they do,
could you please ask them to
give the Tamate Box back to us?
How dare you!
I could never ask them to return a
gift that we gave them for saving us!
I know, but...
If they open it, it'll explode.
Why would you do such a thing?
I'm sorry, but you see,
after the Tomate Box was
stolen ten years ago,
I figured if another thief were to take
it, we ought to teach them a lesson.
I decided to rig the
box with explosives that
would detonate as soon
as the box was opened.
It seemed like a good idea at the time.
But I was wrong,
and since I'm in charge of the Tomate Box
and the rest of the treasure chamber, I...
Very well, I understand.
If Luffy and the others
return with the treasures,
please explain the situation and take the
tomate box back before someone gets hurt.
I do apologize. Oh, dear.
But there's still a chance that
they'll open it before they get back.
Yes, that concerns me as well.
Your Majesty, Minister, an update.
Luffy and the others have just returned.
Ah, so they made it back safely.
That's excellent.
It appears I was worried over nothing.
What?
You gave the treasure to Big Mom?
Luffy!
I had to!
She was gonna wreck the whole island
because she didn't get any candy!
What is her problem?
I mean, if it was me, I'd understand.
Don't worry, I already handled it.
Because I picked up that snail
and gave her a piece of my mind!
Seriously?
Yeah, but no one talks back to her
That's wonderful.
You sure are brave Luffy.
Don't encourage him!
This isn't a good thing!
Please don't yell at me, News!
I told you it's Usa!
Whatever, I'm sorry.
Oh, Luffy, what have you done now?
I'd better sever my bond with Big Mom
before this gets any more complicated.
I understand this may be difficult,
especially for your hard-hitting captain,
but please refrain from
agitating her anymore! No joke!
She's one of the Four Emperors
and I'm way too young to die!
This is even worse than we feared!
What are we going to do now?
If Big Bomb gets that tomate
box and she opens it herself,
it's going to blow up in her
face and then we're screwed!
She'll think Straw Hat's trying to start
trouble and then there'll
be a war on her hands!
We mustn't let that happen!
Well, it's not like you had
any other choice, right?
Yeah, it's already been done now.
Guess you kind of had to stand up to her.
I suppose I can't really
be upset at you over that.
Exactly, I couldn't just let
her punish these guys for...
Still!
I can't believe you gave her
all of the treasure! Mommy!
I'll punch you out!
You did that already!
Okay, here it goes.
To the new world!
We're all gonna die!
I'm already dead, but...
Meanwhile, not far from the
candy factory... Damn it all!
Someone must have picked up the treasures
and ran when I was
knocked out on the ground!
Whoever the thief may be, I'll make
sure they suffer for what they've done!
All I have to do now is confront those
pickpockets and take the riches back again!
With that and the new information
about the mermaid princess,
I can make a good impression for sure.
Wait a minute.
Who are they and what have
they got in those bags?
I knew it! Those are mine!
Just wait till I catch you two.
I'll bury you alive!
I stole those treasures once.
That means I can steal them again!
Pardon?
I feel like I've seen
that ugly mug before.
There he is Says here he's an up-and-comer
Goes by the name Wethead Caribou
Oh, so he's worth 200 million Great,
just when we thought this was over
Yeah, it's too late for
you to beg for mercy
Swamp, Swamp Cat Lincoln
Whee!
Sorry, boys.
That's what happens
when you steal from me!
Scraping!
Huh?
Wait, what?
A turtle?
Devil Fruit power?
Of course.
What else would it be?
A turtle's own type, huh?
Who cares?
You don't scare me!
People with low-geared double fruit
powers always end up dying young.
You fools think that power
makes you invincible and bitter.
Half-bord challenges
are très disappointing.
Alliance, Monsieur Peccombs.
Mama's waiting.
That guy's worth 200
million, and he just...
If I remember, Peccombs has
a bounty of 330 million.
That's pretty scary.
And Big Mom probably makes what he
just did look like child's play.
I sure hope Luffy knows what he's doing.
And somewhere near the red line
in the waters of the new world.
There's another one at two o 'clock.
Fire ships are popping up
all over the place, sir.
What the hell is this?
trying to get on a good side
you suck up mind your own
business they finally set me
free from that living hell.
I can't die now.
Here comes the big one.
Captain, look out.
I'll shield you from arm, Captain.
Out of the way.
I want to do it.
Move.
I got it.
That's our Captain for you.
That was really beautiful, Captain.
Yeah, and the sword play
wasn't half bad either.
Are you taking this seriously or not?
Every one of you should know
how to deflect a bombshell.
There was never a better time to
use that skill than just now, so...
Um, that's a mast.
Here, I cleaned your glasses for you.
Thank you.
She's so cute.
She's like a flower
among this filthy crew.
Don't fool around in the middle of combat.
You'll get yourselves killed.
The G5 is such a joke and to
think you're all Navy soldiers
you had better not take me lightly
just because I'm a woman. Oh.
Captain Toshiki you're
just so adorable how can I
not respect you that's exactly
the kind of treatment I
mean there's a difference
between respect and whatever
you keep it down to shiki
i'm busy my apologies sir i
see so a pirate from the
seafloor named Heart jones
took you captive that explains
a lot that must be why
there were no rookies passing
through fishman island
recently took us captive i wish
he made us his slaves Heart
stirred up some kind of
civil war on fish man island
he made us fight for his
side and then this group of
pirates set us free a group
of pirates yeah but i'm not
telling you who don't be
stupid can't you see who we're
dealing with they're not just
navy soldiers they're the
g5 they use pirates as bait
when they fish for sharks
or even as kindling for a
bonfire they're the rogue
unit of the navy they don't
even obey orders from HQ!
Trust me, you have no idea how
ruthless these bastards are!
Of all the people to be caught by,
we had to end up in the hands of
the notorious White Chase Smoker!
Well, Vice Admiral, can
we take over from here?
No, I beg you!
I'll tell you everything!
Please have mercy!
The ones who defeated
Heart Jones and his crew!
It was the Straw Hat Pirates, okay?
I know that already, idiot.
Madam Charlie, Luffy and his
friends are setting sail now.
Oh?
Perhaps you should see
them off. Sure thing!
Wait up!
We wanna go say goodbye too!
Sorry, but I need somebody to
stay here and run the cafe.
We'll have more tourists here now that
we're rid of that despicable Heart.
So I need you girls to keep this
place in tip-top shape for me, okay?
You got it, Madam Charlie.
Ah the crystal ball.
Don't worry.
I'm through with that now.
I don't need to look
into the future. Anymore.
After all, fishman island being
torn apart by Straw Hat luffy.
Well, that's a future
I never wanted to see.
So if my prediction turned
out to be incorrect this time,
then nothing would make me happier.
She knows her visions are never wrong.
She must be more scared than anyone.
And it may not come true anytime soon.
It could be tomorrow or a year from now.
So we don't know when
we can stop worrying.
Look, madam. Charlie.
I know you're afraid.
But luffy chin and the
others would never Kuma.
I hope that you forgive me.
I shouldn't have suspected your friends.
I see that now.
So you'd like me to trust
the Straw Hat boy then?
Here you go, for your trip.
Sweet! Thanks, everybody!
Oh, Luffy, do you really have to
set sail from here immediately?
I only just met you.
Stay with us at least one more day.
No, better yet, another week.
Or a year, perhaps?
Jeez, Weepy Hachi, you haven't stopped
crying since the moment we met, have you?
You're right, I'm always a crybaby.
I'm sorry, Luffy.
Wow, I can't believe my
fantasy is finally coming true!
The beautiful mermaid princess is in
tears because she can't bear to see me go!
Forget the new world,
I'm happy right here!
I agree.
In fact, our time with these ladies
has inspired me to compose a new song.
I met my girlfriend at the Mermaid Café.
Try not to cry!
I always have a place in my
heart for every one of you!
I like that idea.
Maybe you should stay here.
I don't want to watch you
drown in your own nosebleeds.
You're just jealous because they're
not making you to stay, ugly!
Who are you calling ugly?
Your Majesty.
Should you tell them or should I?
It's only a matter of time
until the tomate box reaches.
They need to know.
If Big Mom opens the box, it'll explode.
Yes, but look at them.
It's all over.
We can't go to the New World now.
Big Mom's gonna murder us
the second we get there.
Maybe if we start sending
her every piece of
treasure we find for
the rest of our lives,
And she might let it slide just this way.
If we tell them they sent her a bomb,
they'll lose their will to live.
Come to think of it, Minister of the
Right, those explosives are ten years old.
It's possible they're
no longer functional.
Oh, I admire your
positivity, Your Majesty.
We do keep it rather humid in
the Ryugu Palace, after all.
And who really knows if Big Mom
will open the box herself anyway.
Right, then let's just hope for the best.
Do I want to know what you
two are whispering about?
Uh, what's this?
It's a Log Pose for the new world.
I'd like you to take it with you.
It frightened me to think that the one
you'd be using had only a single needle.
What's up, Nami?
So you got a new Log Pose?
Whoa, it looks pretty cool.
But why does it have three needles?
Well, take a look at the
long poles on your wrist.
Noticed anything odd?
It's still moving. That's funny.
I thought we had stayed here
long enough for it to stabilize.
Oh, no, you did.
Half a day is all you need,
but that's not the issue.
For the first half of your journey,
the long poles was recording the
magnetic waves of each destination,
so you were able to navigate
between islands that way.
However, the second half of the Grand
Line won't be so easy to predict.
In addition to the
currents and the weather,
some of the islands tend to experience
changes in their magnetic waves as well. Huh?
In fact, some islands have
waves that disappear altogether.
Huh?
Then how are we supposed
to find out where they are?
Well, you're sure to lose
your way with only one needle.
But now, fortunately,
you have three of them.
Okay, so why is one of the needles moving
while the other two are sitting still?
Are you sure this thing works?
Each of the needles is
recording the magnetic
waves from one of three
different islands. This way,
you'll be able to assess
multiple paths and determine
which way to travel based on
your instincts as a navigator.
It's likely to make the difference
between life and death for you.
A skilled navigator will know
which direction is safest by
simply observing the slightest
movement of their needles.
There are no guarantees, but there is
a good rule of thumb you can follow.
Erratic movement means more danger.
Changes in magnetic waves are often
caused by abnormalities on the island.
What?
That's creepy.
I'd rather not know that stuff, thank you.
I'm with you on this one. Me too.
Why don't you go ahead
and smash that thing now?
But you mustn't.
Knowing where the danger is will
help you travel more safely.
Let me see you night!
No! Luffy!
Little one's going crazy!
That must be where the
party is, I say we go there!
We're gonna die!
Excuse me, but who's the
navigator around here?
I don't try to do your job, do I?
So let me do mine!
Yeah, well I'm the captain, remember?
Uh, Captain Luffy, we like being
alive, so please listen to her, okay?
Don't be afraid, Nami, I'll protect you!
Oh, look at her, she's so adorable!
And now for the B-Sun, I
call it rightfully a boss!
Yo!
Are you ready?
Because it's time to get
this show on the road, bro!
Huh?
Den taught me how to bring
this baby back up to the top!
Well, Luffy?
Right!
Let's go!
We'll miss you!
See ya!
No!
I'm gonna stay here and help
these folks rebuild the factory.
You sure you'll be all
right without a guide?
Sure, and there's fun having you
around, but I think we'll be okay.
Oh, sure, screw it!
We don't need a guide!
I mean, what's the point?
Apparently we're just
gonna waltz our way into
the world of suffering
and death anyway Exactly!
Why don't we all just die right now
and save ourselves in trouble, huh?
Oh dear
Goodbye!
Come back someday!
You bet your sweet fins I will!
You ladies are all I dream about!
So much for the all blue
You've done so much to help
our kingdom. We thank you
I pray that you will arrive safely.
Thanks?
Just you wait!
By next time, woo!
We'll be way tougher!
Even tougher than the
Great Knight Neptune,
and we'll be commanding the most
powerful army under the Cephas.
Hell, Dorry!
Sounds good!
Now, where's...
There he is!
All right, new world, here we come!
It's time to set sail!
Goodbye, Sawhat!
Some more candy and meat sometime!
I like humans now!
Oh, and robots and raccoons too!
I'm reindeer, but I'll let that one go.
Not me? Be careful!
Come back any time!
Come back for more takoyaki, okay?
I love you!
Every one of you!
Ready!
Challenge you!
And remember!
I just wanted to say, if
I get to see you again,
then I promise you, I won't cry.
At least not as much as now.
I hope you and I can take
another stroll together, Luffy.
Oh, yeah?
Huh?
You want to go back to
your mom's grave again?
No, not this time.
The place I want to go is farther away.
I want to visit a real forest.
On the surface.
That's right.
You've never been out of
the sea before, have you?
Sure, let's do it.
I'll take you there first chance I get.
Oh, no.
Promise me.
Okay, I'll thank you, Sweria.
Leave it to me.
Careful now, Luffy.
If you make a promise, we
have to help you keep it.
Remember, no matter what happens,
you must never break a promise, ever.
You know what, though?
Count me in.
Oh, not me.
And me, of course.
Yeah, me too.
And me.
Me too.
Don't forget me.
We've all given our word now.
No bones about that.
We won't let you down.
So don't cry anymore? Okay!
Right!
Never forget what they've done for us.
We won't, Father.
Hey, Papa!
Can you pretty please
buy me a Straw Hat, too?
I want to be just like Luffy.
I'm sorry buddy, but they don't
sell Straw Hats on the sea floor.
Then go get one from up there!
I can't do that, son.
The surface is full of
humans who hate our kind.
There's no telling what they'll do if I.
What I mean is.
I've heard that some
humans aren't very nice.
That's all.
But they're not all the same.
Some of them are heroes,
like Straw Hat Luffy.
Hey, Boss Jinbei.
Perfect timing!
I just overheard.
I'm going to ask a merchant to get his
hands on some of those Straw Hats for us.
Really?
Yes, my boy.
You'd like to be a hero, wouldn't you?
Uh-huh.
I miss it already!
All those gorgeous mermaids!
Look alive, you guys! Don't goof off!
Once we ascend, who knows what
trouble we might run into?
You remember how scary it was
on the way down, don't you?
Huh?
What's with the weird boxes, Franky?
Those are hollow cubes made out of Banyan.
They're gonna help us float.
I can even adjust the ship's
speed based on how many I throw.
Luffy, what's up?
Once we reach the new world...
Shanks won't be far away.
I hope I see him soon.
In that case, I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than anything else.
I want you to bring this hat back to me,
but not until you become a great pirate.
There is one thing that hurts.
I won't be around to see
you fulfill your dream.
That's fine.
I have faith.
You can do it.
Because you're my brother.
There is yet joy beyond your sorrow.
What's gone may be gone.
But you still have something left in
this world to treasure, don't you?
Let nothing stop you
from reaching the top.
By the way,
I was wondering if you've
ever heard the name
they use for the second
half of the Grand Line.
On the other side of the red line,
at the far reaches of the ocean,
is a place that few pirates
or marines have ever seen.
They call it the New World.
The New World.
There's a new era coming,
and the people who can guide
it are gathering on those seas.
They say the one who can master those
waters will become king of the pirates.
Who knows what's waiting for us up there?
That's the greatest sea in the world!
Took long enough.
I'm ready for some action.
It won't be long now, Laboon.
Just one half to go.
With this new lug pose,
I can take us anywhere.
And wherever we go,
the Snow can handle it.
Don't worry, I'll treat all your injuries!
And as long as I'm around,
you'll never go hungry.
The great Usam's got your back, too!
All right!
Let's go!
New World Waiting!
Yeah!